{
    "mc" : [
        {
            "name" : "mc1",
            "question" : "Which of the following is an available extension for PHP?",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) .phpht"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) .php4"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) .phpj"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) .php3"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "d"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc2",
            "question" : "A PHP script begins with ____ and ends with _____.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) &lt;?php , php&gt;"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) &lt;? , php&gt;"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) &lt;?php , ?&gt;"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) &lt;php , php&gt;"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "c"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc3",
            "question" : "All the tags that are included in the PHP script through the print or echo command will be interpreted by the browser as _____.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) HTML"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) JavaScript"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) Node"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) CSS"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc4",
            "question" : "In a PHP script, what is the symbol at the beginning when you are going to declare a variable?",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) ?"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) *"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) %"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) $"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "d"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc5",
            "question" : "What do you call the process when assigning a value into a variable that it is declared?",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) Declaration"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) Initialization"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) Partition"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) Synchronization"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "d"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc6",
            "question" : "In PHP, these are variables that has been placed in between the parenthesis of a function.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) Parameters"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) Methods"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) Classes"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) Interfaces"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc7",
            "question" : "In PHP, what is the keyword being used in returning a value in a function?",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) returnValue"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) return"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) recurValue"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) recur"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc8",
            "question" : "In a PHP script, what is the keyword that is being used to make sure that a switch statement is not going to go down to the next value.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) Break"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) Stop"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) End"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) Snap"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc9",
            "question" : "The first part of a loop in PHP that initializes variable is called?",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) Condition"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) Increment statement"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) Variable declaration"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) Increment"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "c"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc10",
            "question" : "In a PHP script, it is the keyword used in stopping a loop and will continue to the next from its beginning.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) Stop"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) Continue"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) Reset"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) Break"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        }
    ],

    "tf" : [
        {
            "name" : "tf1",
            "question" : "In PHP a session can be started by calling the session_start() function.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf2",
            "question" : "To destroy a PHP Session use a function called session_delete().",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf3",
            "question" : "Set the value of session.auto_start to 1 in the php.ini file.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf4",
            "question" : "To set cookies in PHP use the function cookieset().",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },{
            "name" : "tf5",
            "question" : "PHP was originally called PHP/FI which means Personal Home Page/Forms Interpreter.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf6",
            "question" : "PHP stands for Port Hypertext Processor.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf7",
            "question" : "PHP files have an extension of .php, .phtml, and .php3.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf8",
            "question" : "On PHP, write command is what you use to print a text on a webpage.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf9",
            "question" : "In PHP, the comments are being declared for the code for it to be easier to understand.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf10",
            "question" : "PHP is static and is an open source scripting language.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        }
    ],

    "iden" : [
        {
            "name" : "iden1",
            "question" : "This variable is used by PHP for storing information or changing the settings for the user.",
            "correctAnswer" : "session"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden2",
            "question" : "What function in PHP are you going to use to store the information by starting it.",
            "correctAnswer" : "session_start()"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden3",
            "question" : "He/She designed the PHP or Hypertext Preprocessor",
            "correctAnswer" : "Rasmus Lerdorf"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden4",
            "question" : "It is the functionality has been added or has been improved on PHP3 to make PHP4.",
            "correctAnswer" : "Object-oriented programming"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden5",
            "question" : "It is a scripting language that is most suited to a server-side web development.",
            "correctAnswer" : "PHP"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden6",
            "question" : "The function that you will be using to set cookies in PHP.",
            "correctAnswer" : "setcookie()"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden7",
            "question" : "These are superglobals that is being used by PHP to collect form-data. <em>(please include an ' and ' in between your answers) </em>",
            "correctAnswer" : "GET and POST"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden8",
            "question" : "This tool shows both the source code of php and the output code of HTML.",
            "correctAnswer" : "Show PHP"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden9",
            "question" : "When information is sent to this method, it will be visible to everyone.",
            "correctAnswer" : "GET method"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden10",
            "question" : "When information is sent to this method, it will be invisible to everyone.",
            "correctAnswer" : "POST method"
        }
    ]
}